https://www.puzzlewarehouse.com/privacy/

Account
Cart (0)
Gift Cards
Not sure what to get? Cards starting at $10.
Puzzle Clubs
FOR THOSE WHO LOVE PUZZLES!
Join the Puzzle Club and receive a new jigsaw puzzle every month as long as your membership is active.
Choose between monthly, 6 months or annually along with your piece count and we will do the rest!
Privacy Policy
Some websites hide their practices from their customers and visitors.  We prefer honesty.In order to power relevant, interest-based content and advertisements for you, we need partners to help us identify you when you interact with us. Our partners may collect non-personal information like your IP address, device ID, shopping behavior, and information about your browser or operating system. We may share information about you such as your email or other identifiers with our partners. If we do, we always share it in a non-human-readable form to ensure the security of your information. Our partners may combine our personal and non-personal information about you with information from other sources, and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser, all to help us communicate better with you.We also care about choice. You can opt-out of these services at any time;To opt-out of BouncePilot’s services, please go to http://BouncePilot.com/opt-out/. To opt-out of LiveRamp’s services, please go to http://www.liveramp.com/opt_out. To opt-out of third party cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices. To opt-out of the use of your mobile device ID for targeted advertising, please see http://www.aboutads.info/appchoices.Safe Shopping GuaranteeThe Puzzle Warehouse Safe Shopping Guarantee protects you while you shop at Puzzle Warehouse so that you never have to worry about credit card safety. Period.We guarantee that every transaction you make at Puzzle Warehouse will be safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at Puzzle Warehouse. Why is Puzzle Warehouse so safe?Safety in Numbers: When you shop at Puzzle Warehouse, you'll be one of the thousands of customers who have safely shopped with us without credit card fraud.Safe Technology: Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is provided by Google, one of the world's leading providers of Internet trust services and we believe it is the best software available today for secure online commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. You can rest assured that your personal information is safe.You still don't want to use your credit card on the Internet?No problem. Just call us at 866-539-4278 and one of our outstanding customer service representatives will be glad to take your order.Guarantee Details:Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50, Puzzle Warehouse will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50. Puzzle Warehouse will cover this liability only if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made at Puzzle Warehouse while using the secure server.In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures.Any questions about our privacy policy? Give us a call or email us at support@puzzlewarehouse.com we are here to answer any questions you have!Party Games1000 Piece PuzzlesLarge Piece PuzzlesOn Sale Items
Your Order
Track My Order
Returns
My Account
Wish List
Help
Shipping Information
About Us
Copyright © 2008-2020, Puzzle Warehouse, All rights reserved.
Puzzle Warehouse recycles everything it can to save the environment and to keep costs and prices low.
We are hiring! Please fill out the employment form or send your resume to careers@puzzlewarehouse.com.
Add User Survey
×
Are you a Puzzle Warehouse customer? Login to submit your user survey!
How likely are you to recommend Puzzle Warehouse to a friend or colleague?
What is your email address?
Is there anything else you'd like to share?
Would you like a reply to this email?
Yes
No
Submit User Survey
Thank you for submitting your user survey! Please allow up to one week for surveys to be added.
